Sevilla one, Barcelona three.
Let's welcome in, shall we? Luis Garcia,
former Barcelona player, who is
absolutely loving it at the moment,
Luis. And why not? They are the best
team in the world, and there isn't
really a question about it at the
moment.
>> No, I don't think so, Dan. I think that
we are all enjoying everyone who loves
football needs to have to enjoy
this momentum that Barcelona is in. I
think they've been brilliant the whole
start of the season. And we saw what
they've been doing for the past 2 years.
We had a lot of talks and discussion
about Hansi Flick, his high line, that
intensity on the field, the problem that
they faced
later in March when they arrived some of
the players that are involved in the
last stage of Champions League. But
right now, at the moment, by what we can
see, the results and the numbers, we
have to say that Barcelona is probably
the best
the best team in the world. And the
first 45 they were quite intense. I
think that Sevilla did a pretty good
job, really good shape. They managed to
to hold Barcelona. They they wasn't
having that fluidity that we are used to
see. Pedri wasn't getting involved, and
when he was involved he was a little bit
sloppy. Anthony Gordon there on the left
side didn't appear. And Lamela was
confronting a few moments with the
crowd, with the players, with the
faults, because Sevilla was trying to be
physical.
>> [snorts]
>> And in the second half, when the
intensity of Sevilla dropped a little
bit, then is when Barcelona start
pushing higher, controlling more, and
dominating more, and the goals were
arriving. And what to say about Fati?
Well, I think we we talked a lot about
it. I think that he's right now one of
the best players, if not the best player
in the world. He's in a great moment.
>> You called it actually at half time,
Casey, when we were talking about how
resilient Sevilla were in the opening.
You said, "Let's see what energy they
have in the second half." Because to
play like that against Barcelona for 90
minutes is near on impossible, cuz
you're trying to contain them all the
time, and there's only so much gas in
the tank.
>> There is. And And you know, it's still
a little bit warm in in Sevilla this
time of year. It was in the 80s.
>> Yeah.
Um
you look you saw in the end 70%
possession.
Granted, Shaka and I watched a lot of
guys run, but um
it's it's always easier to run with the
ball than it is without the ball. And
there's there's just that time over and
over again, running running running.
And and and I think what happened
because they were a little more tired,
they didn't control the second balls in
the second half the way they did in that
first half, which then gave more of the
ball to Barcelona, which then gave more
of the opportunity to make the runs off
the ball. And then when you have the
quality of finish,
first of all, the quality of the setup
from Lamine Yamal off of winning a
second ball in the box, but then having
three guys around you and finding a way
to put a perfect cross in for Raphinha.
Then, the perfect pass when you think,
"I know he's going to check and run. I
know he's going to do it, and I can't do
anything about it."
>> Uh Raphinha scoring the perfect
hat-trick.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh Shaka, Lionel Messi didn't do that at
all during his 32 hat-tricks.
>> How How was that How was that How
[laughter] was that How was that a
thing?
>> Well, you were saying before that that
makes for you Raphinha better than
Messi.
>> [laughter]
>> It says Ah, boy. Um I have no idea how
we how how we got here.
>> Hey, I'll tell you what, Shaka. If you
had to pay to watch anyone at the
moment,
>> Ronaldo is the best player in the world.
>> He is so full of confidence, just seems
to be in the right place at the right
time.
>> And he And he And he's such a
non-traditional number nine that he's
giving defenses more problems than than
they used to.
He can drop off and pick up the ball in
the half spaces. As you saw again,
twice, he can run off the shoulder of
defenders.
Um and once he does get that right side,
once he is onside, you cannot catch him.
And you saw for a second, he just has
that timing and that instinct of a a
number nine. So, the question becomes
how do you play Raphinha? How do you
play up against this Barcelona? You've
seen the approach from Sevilla today to
try to press a little bit higher up, to
try to be a little bit more aggressive.
You've seen earlier this season teams
kind of dropping off and playing in a
low block.
And the result has has has been the same
to to the point Sevilla only conceding
three. That you almost want to celebrate
that kind of given what we've seen so
far this season. And Barcelona have just
been the best team bar none. I know the
caveat is they haven't faced any true
test so far this season.
>> a true test. Going to surely this is
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah,
it is.
>> Sevilla best defense in La Liga is
>> Sevilla and and Bilbao, decent teams
where they won by two.
Um
two clear goals in in in both those
those games respectively. But but still,
just everything that Barcelona have to
throw at you. Um um I really don't know
what the correct approach is. Um
let us just sit back and and enjoy it
while it lasts.
>> I think praying I think it's [laughter]
about
I don't know.
>> One of the things I like Luis, it's
interesting that the point that Shaka
brings up. He says he won't trust
Barcelona until they play someone
decent. [laughter]
Is is that is that fair? Because that
that's been shared by others as well.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, well, I think that the
so far the the the games that they
played they've been quite easy to to
play. They were quite soft. They they
haven't been tested probably because
it's true that sometimes you get
exposed, sometimes they concede and
today they could have a concede one or
two goals and in the previous game
exactly same. But they are not doing it.
They maybe concede one or maybe
not many chances. But in the end this
Barcelona side, I think and I agree with
the guy they haven't been tested
probably in Champions League later on
when the the the big teams arrive and
then they have to put everything and
then we will realize really what it is
the that the best 11 for this Barcelona
side because at the moment we don't know
if it's Gavi or
or Pedri. Is that Yemmy? Is that
partnership in the middle with Fermin
and and and Dani Olmo is the right one?
The other team I think at the back maybe
you you have some doubts. So so far
we've seen a very good Barcelona but I
agree with the guys. I think they
haven't been tested properly. We'll need
to wait and see.